(Stuart:)Oh, I see you guys have found
my little treasure.
Yeah, pfft, it's okay, I guess.
(Leonard:)Buh-buh-buh-buh.
(Leonard:)What do you want for it?
(Stuart:)Oh, it's hard to
put a price on something...
(Stuart:)...that's a copy of something
that was on pay cable.
(Stuart:)But for my friends, let's say 250.
- Ooh, that's pretty steep.
- It's a limited edition.
(Stuart:)They only made 8000 of these
bad boys.
(Sheldon:)Only 8000.
We're wasting precious time. Buy it.
(Leonard:)Hang on. Can you do any better?
(Stuart:)I'm already giving
you the friends and family discount.
(Sheldon:)Oh, did you hear that?
The friends and family discount.
We are honored and we will take it.
(Leonard:)Slow down. Two hundred.
(Sheldon:)What are you doing?
250 is already a discounted price.
- Will you shut up?
- Tell you what, I'll go 235.
(Leonard:)Nope. Maybe another time.
- Okay, 225, my final offer.
- Take it, take it.